mathspace.co 2016-05-30

# Mathspace :: Our Privacy Policy

Mathspace is dedicated to protecting the privacy and security of our users ( **Registrants** ) on our website (the **Site** ). In order to understand how your personal information is collected and used by us ( **Mathspace** ), please read through this Privacy Policy carefully. Prior to registration, Registrants must agree to have their personal information used by Mathspace, as set out by this Privacy Policy. Users under the age of 18 years old will need to gain consent from a parent or guardian prior to giving us their personal information. Mathspace recommends Registrants under the age of 18 review the Privacy Policy with their parents or guardians. Registrants, please make sure you understand the content contained within this Privacy Policy. Mathspace notes that any terms which are not defined within this Policy have the meaning given to them by the English dictionary.

### What does the Privacy Policy cover?

The Privacy Policy explains how Mathspace collects and uses information provided by its users, including the use of the personal information provided by our Registrants. With re-spect to personal information, Mathspace is referring to information which is personally iden-tifiable to the Registrant.

### What does Mathspace do with the information collected by its Registrants?

#### Information you knowingly provide us with

If you choose to subscribe with Mathspace, you will be asked to provide us with details to create a username:

  * The following details are mandatory: School name
  * The following details are recommended, but not mandatory: First name, last name (if not provided, de-identified accounts can be created)
  * The following details are optional: student email address, parent email address

You will also be permitted to input a profile picture (optional input). Mathspace notes that this information can only be viewed by your "Limited Access Group" (students and teacher of your registrant school). A Registrants pro-file cannot be viewed by those that are not within its selected Limited Access Group.

#### Information collected during your use of Mathspace

In addition to the information you knowingly provide, Mathspace receives and stores other information each time a Registrant uses the Service. This information includes:

  * Information submitted by users of the Site through online forms, surveys, blogs or other interactive tools that may be featured on the Site periodically. 
  * Offline information about you, if you contact Mathspace by fax, mail or telephone. 
  * Information about your usage of the Site.
  * Mathspace cookie information and your IP address.

### What your personal information is used for?

Information you provide to Mathspace will be used to:

  * Provide you with access to our site and other information or services you require 
  * Send a confirmation of subscription to our services
  * Contact you regarding feedback or follow-up on your usage of our site and services 
  * Respond to your questions and concerns regarding our Site and services 
  * Publish first names and last initial of top achievers on the Site, and to send out prizes. 
  * Collect and analyse information in order to develop and improve our services, and en-hance user experience of our Site. 

### What your personal information is NOT used for?

Personal information that has been collected by us will be kept strictly confidential, and will not be sold or deliberately shared with any third parties without your consent UNLESS:

  * Required or permitted by law (such as a subpoena or court order) 
  * We share collective data about usage of our Site. This information is anonymous, and does not contain any information that can be used to identify individuals. 

### What information can our Registrants access?

Mathspace allows its Registrants to access the following information about itself for the pur-pose of viewing and updating the Registrant’s personal information, as well as information relating to the Registrants progress and results. The Registrant will also be able view the names and profile pictures of other members of its selected Limited Access Group. Math-space notes that students and teacher Registrants within the selected Limited Access Group will be able to access student results and progression.

### Site cookies

Our Site employs the use of cookies, which are small files that are stored on your computer. There are two types of cookies: session cookies and stored cookies. Session cookies are au-tomatically deleted when you close your browser, while stored cookies are retained for future browsing sessions.

They allow our Site to remember Registrants on subsequent visits, by linking you to your ac-count and user preferences. The cookies are not linked to any personal information you pro-vide. Users are able to adjust their browser preferences to restrict or block cookies. This will not affect your access to our Site.

### Display of names

To provide an engaging learning environment by acknowledging achievements, Mathspace publishes names of top achieving students on the leader board. However, such information will not identify individuals as full names and/or profile pictures will not be released outside a Registrant’s Limited Access Group.

### Your rights

Registrants have the right to withdraw from any mailing lists, and to amend any incorrect personal information. You may request to see personal information that we have collected about you at any time. To maintain an up-to-date and accurate website, please notify us of any changes to your contact information.

### Our responsibilities

We strive to keep your personal information safe and confidential by implementing appropri-ate security measures against theft, accidental damage or loss. Your personal information will be kept by Mathspace for the period that it is needed (purposes as outlined in this Privacy Policy), or unless otherwise specified by law.

### Revisions to our Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy may be updated periodically to continue to align to privacy legislation. Mathspace will contact users if any policy change diminishes privacy rights that they were entitled to prior to those policy changes.

### Third-party websites

Our Site may provide links that navigate you to third-party websites; our Privacy Policy does not apply to such linked sites, and it is highly advised that you refer to the appropriate web-site’s Privacy Policy.

### More information

If you would like to find out more about privacy laws and guidelines, visit www.privacy.gov.au.
